{
    "subject": "resource/Jim_Webb",
    "predicate": "ontology/award",
    "object": "resource/Silver_Star",
    "human_readable": "Jim Webb was awarded a Silver Star.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9835050702095032,
            "question": "For what achievement was Jim Webb awarded a Silver Star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9813709855079651,
            "question": "When was Jim Webb awarded the Silver Star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8668639063835144,
            "question": "Who received a Silver Star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7287014126777649,
            "question": "What award did Jim Webb receive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5656142830848694,
            "question": "What is significant about receiving a Silver Star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43034887313842773,
            "question": "What does a Silver Star represent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3588782250881195,
            "question": "Is a Silver Star a military decoration?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13663172721862793,
            "question": "What branch of the military did Jim Webb serve in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.014827830716967583,
            "question": "What are some other examples of high military honors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.011341913603246212,
            "question": "Are there different ranks of military decorations?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jim Webb was awarded a Silver Star.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6829_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some other examples of high military honors?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6829_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What branch of the military did Jim Webb serve in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6829_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is a Silver Star a military decoration?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6829_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6829_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6829_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6829_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6829_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6829_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6829_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6829_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6829_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6829_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6829_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to document 106.txt, Jim Webb \"...was awarded the Silver Star...\" and according to document 49.txt, Editor's Note mentions that \"as a rifle platoon and company commander in the infamous An Hoa Basin west of Danang he was awarded the Navy Cross, the Silver Star Medal...\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information mentions that Jim Webb was \"awarded the Silver Star, two Bronze Stars and two Purple Hearts\" during his service in Vietnam. Therefore, the statement \"Jim Webb was awarded a Silver Star\" is supported by the documents provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}